Guide to the Forest Hills Gardens Corporation Records, 1922-1979, 1922-1958 (bulk)
Forest Hills Gardens Corporation Records
- Alphabetical Files
  - 1940-1944
    - 1941
      - Streets, 1941 (Box 7)
        Closings, pavings (some photographs)
      - T - Correspondence, 1941 (Box 7)
      - Taxi Association, 1941 (Box 7)
      - Taxi Association Matters, 1932-1941 (Box 7)
        Especially with regard to booth
      - Trial Balance - Bookkeeping, 1941 (Box 7)
      - Treasurer's Reports, 1941 (Box 7)
        Bookkeeping details and audit for 1941
      - U - Correspondence, 1941 (Box 6)
      - Upkeep Committee, 1941 (Box 6)
        Payrolls, inventory, reports, complaints
      - V - Correspondence, 1941 (Box 6)
      - W - Correspondence, 1941 (Box 6)
      - Waivers of Restrictions, 1941 (Box 6)
        Waivers with various homeowners, copy of FHG Bulletin - Christmas 1924, copy of FHG Bulletin - July 14, 1917 (with pictures of Col. Roosevelt speaking in Station Square July 4, 1917 )
      - XYZ - Correspondence, 1941 (Box 6)
    - 1942
      - A, B, and C - Correspondence, 1942 (Box 21)
        Includes sales brochure from Leslie Apartments
      - Boyce, 1942 (Box 4)
        Law Committee reports, FHGDC works, annual meeting address, correspondence
      - Committee Reports, 1942 (Box 21)
      - D, E, F, and G - Correspondence, 1942 (Box 21)
      - Defense Committee, 1942 (Box 4)
        Correspondence regarding OCD, victory gardens, FHGDC, air raid and emergency plans
      - Green, Laura M., 1936-1939 (Box 21)
        Includes "News of Gardens Corporation, November 1938
      - H, I, J, K, L, Lampposts - Correspondence, 1942 (Box 21)
      - Insurance (Box 21)
        Includes condition survey of FHG streets dated May 19, 1934
      - M, N, O, P, Q, and R - Correspondence, 1942 (Box 21)
      - Orders, Invoices & Receipts, 1942 (Box 21)
      - Publicity, 1942 (Box 21)
        Also complete collection of News of Gardens Corporation 1931-1941
      - Streets, 1942 (Box 21)
        Includes photos of July 4 celebration
      - T, U, V, W, XYZ - Correspondence, 1942 (Box 21)
      - Treasurer's Reports, 1942 (Box 21)
      - Upkeep Committee, 1942 (Box 21)
      - Upkeep Brochures, 1940s (Box 21)
      - Willsin, 1942 (Box 21)
        Development of Willsin plot, corner of Terraces and Middle May Place includes architectural rendering, also plans for Cook, Albert Homes, Inc. and Dietsche (agreements modifying restrictions)
    - 1943
      - A - Correspondence, 1943 (Box 4)
      - B - Correspondence, 1943 (Box 4)
      - C - Reports, 1943 (Box 4)
      - Committee Reports, 1943 (Box 4)
        Monthly and annual meeting reports
      - D - Correspondence, 1943 (Box 4)
      - E - Correspondence, 1943 (Box 4)
      - F - Correspondence, 1943 (Box 4)
      - G - Correspondence, 1943 (Box 4)
      - H - Correspondence, 1943 (Box 4)
      - Help, 1943 (Box 4)
        FHG employees and services
      - I - Correspondence, 1943 (Box 4)
        Memoranda and correspondence regarding Ives-Quinn anti-discrimination bill (then pending - concerned with discrimination in employment)
      - Insurance (policies), 1943 (Box 4)
      - J - Correspondence, 1943 (Box 4)
      - K, L, M, and N - Correspondence, 1943 (Box 21)
      - Lampposts, 1943 (Box 4)
        Regarding wartime dimming of lights, replacements of posts, etc.
      - O, P, Q, R - Correspondence, 1943 (Box 21)
      - Orders, Invoices & Receipts, 1943 (Box 21)
      - Mr. Reydel (director), 1943 (Box 3)
      - S - Correspondence, 1943 (Box 21)
      - Streets, 1943 (Box 21)
      - Parks, 1942-1943 (Box 21)
      - T - Correspondence, 1943 (Box 23)
      - Treasurer's Report, 1943 (Box 23)
      - Trial Balance, 1943 (Box 23)
      - U - Correspondence, 1943 (Box 23)
      - Upkeep Committee, 1943 (Box 23)
        Time sheets, inventory, correspondence, reports
      - V - Correspondence, 1943 (Box 23)
      - W - Correspondence, 1943 (Box 23)
      - Waivers of Restrictions, 1943 (Box 23)
        Smith, Zand, Doppel, Paley, Jean, Moeller, Connolly
      - XYZ - Correspondence, 1943 (Box 23)
    - 1944
      - A - Correspondence, 1944 (Box 10)
      - B - Correspondence, 1944 (Box 10)
      - Boyer - Law committee reports for Judge Boyce, 1944 (Box 10)
      - C - Correspondence, 1944 (Box 10)
      - Circulars, 1944 (Box 10)
        Objections to distribution in Gardens
      - Committee Reports and minutes of Board Meetings, 1944 (Box 10)
      - D - Correspondence, 1944 (Box 10)
      - E - Correspondence, 1944 (Box 10)
      - F - Correspondence, 1944 (Box 10)
      - G - Correspondence, 1944 (Box 10)
      - H - Correspondence, 1944 (Box 10)
      - Help, 1944 (Box 10)
        Correspondence regarding Gardens' employees and contractors
      - Hof, 1938-1945 (Box 10)
        Correspondence regarding Mr. Hof arrears and foreclosure in various properties
      - Insurance, 1944 (Box 10)
      - J - Correspondence, 1944 (Box 10)
      - K - Correspondence, 1944 (Box 10)
      - L - Correspondence, 1944 (Box 10)
      - M - Correspondence, 1944 (Box 10)
      - Mc - Correspondence, 1944 (Box 10)
      - N - Correspondence, 1944 (Box 10)
      - O - Correspondence, 1944 (Box 10)
      - Orders - Correspondence regarding office equipment, 1944 (Box 10)
      - P - Correspondence, 1944 (Box 10)
      - Parks, 1944 (Box 10)
        Lists of card holders, apartment tenants
      - R - Correspondence, 1944 (Box 10)
      - S - Correspondence, 1944 (Box 10)
      - Streets, 1944 (Box 10)
        Regarding use of private streets
      - Mr. Stokes, 1943 (Box 10)
        Single letter regarding "Victory tax"
      - T - Correspondence, 1944 (Box 10)
      - Treasurers Reports, 1944 (Box 10)
        Audit and accounting statements, inventories
      - Trial Balance, 1944 (Box 10)
      - U - Correspondence, 1944 (Box 10)
        Single Upkeep Committee Report
      - V - Correspondence, 1944 (Box 10)
      - W - Correspondence, 1944 (Box 10)
        Survey map of West Side Tennis Club, Stadium concerts correspondence
      - Waivers of Restrictions, 1944 (Box 10)
      - XYZ - Correspondence, 1944 (Box 10)
  - 1945-1950
    - 1945
      - A - Correspondence, 1945 (Box 26)
      - B - Correspondence, 1945 (Box 26)
      - Boyce (Director), 1945 (Box 26)
        Includes Law Committee reports
      - Car Licenses, 1945 (Box 26)
      - C - Correspondence, 1945 (Box 26)
      - Committee Reports, 1945 (Box 26)
      - Director's Meeting, 1929-1945 (Box 26)
        Includes a large blueprint: Progress Map of FHG and Vanderveer Tract dated Apr. 1, 1926, with revisions of June 1, 1927, May 1, 1928, Jan. 15, 1931; also, a sheet detailing history of ownership of island in Station Square 1928-1931, taken from minutes of Director's Meetings (Deed to FHG recorded)
      - D - Correspondence, 1945 (Box 26)
      - E - Correspondence, 1945 (Box 26)
      - F - Correspondence, 1945 (Box 26)
      - G - Correspondence, 1945 (Box 26)
      - H - Correspondence, 1945 (Box 26)
      - I - Correspondence, 1945 (Box 26)
      - Infringement of Restrictions, 1945 (Box 26)
      - Insurance, 1945 (Box 26)
      - J - Correspondence, 1945 (Box 26)
      - K - Correspondence, 1945 (Box 26)
      - L - Correspondence, 1945 (Box 26)
      - Lampposts, 1945 (Box 26)
        Repairs, claims for damage
      - M - Correspondence, 1945 (Box 26)
      - Mc - Correspondence, 1945 (Box 26)
      - Men's Club, 1945 (Box 26)
      - O - Correspondence, 1945 (Box 26)
      - Orders, 1945 (Box 26)
      - P - Correspondence, 1945 (Box 26)
      - Parks, 1945 (Box 26)
        Park records, cards
      - R - Correspondence, 1945 (Box 26)
      - Gasoline Rationing, 1945 (Box 26)
        Applications for coupons, T coupons, R3 coupons
      - T - Correspondence, 1945 (Box 26)
      - S - Correspondence, 1945 (Box 26)
      - Treasurer's Reports, 1945 (Box 26)
        Bookkeeping details and audit 1945
      - Trial Balance - - Ledger sheets, 1945 (Box 26)
      - Upkeep Committee, 1944-1945 (Box 26)
        Inventories, paving, spraying, payroll
      - V - Correspondence, 1945 (Box 26)
      - W - Correspondence, 1945 (Box 26)
      - Waivers of Restrictions, 1945 (Box 26)
      - XYZ - Correspondence, 1945 (Box 26)
        Regarding zoning changes in MacDonold Park area outside FHG
    - 1946
      - A - Correspondence, 1946 (Box 26)
      - B - Correspondence, 1946 (Box 26)
      - C - Correspondence, 1946 (Box 26)
      - Committee Reports, 1946 (Box 26)
        Architecture, annual meeting
      - Community House, 1940-1946 (Box 26)
      - D - Correspondence, 1946 (Box 26)
      - E - Correspondence, 1946 (Box 26)
      - F - Correspondence, 1946 (Box 26)
      - G - Correspondence, 1946 (Box 26)
      - H - Correspondence, 1946 (Box 26)
      - I - Correspondence, 1946 (Box 26)
      - J - Correspondence, 1946 (Box 26)
      - K - Correspondence, 1946 (Box 26)
      - L - Correspondence, 1946 (Box 26)
      - The Leslie Apartments - Block 12 (brochure), 1942-1947 (Box 26)
      - M - Correspondence, 1946 (Box 26)
      - N - Correspondence, 1946 (Box 26)
      - O - Correspondence, 1946 (Box 26)
      - P - Correspondence, 1946 (Box 26)
      - Parks, 1946 (Box 26)
        Includes lists
      - R - Correspondence, 1946 (Box 26)
      - S - Correspondence, 1946 (Box 3)
      - Stokes, 1946 (Box 3)
        Letter regarding tax on membership dues (should not be taxed)
      - Streets, 1946 (Box 3)
        Creation of one-way streets in Forest Hills area (copy of City Record), correspondence regarding bus routes, Celebrations Assoc.
      - T - Correspondence, 1946 (Box 8)
      - Taxi Association, 1943 (Box 3)
      - Taxpayers Association (Box 3)
      - Treasurers Reports - Bookkeeping and audit, 1946 (Box 8)
      - Trial Balance - Bookkeeping records, 1946 (Box 8)
      - Upkeep Committee, 1946 (Box 3)
        Reports, inventories, vouchers, correspondence
      - V - Correspondence, 1946 (Box 3)
      - W - Correspondence, 1946 (Box 3)
      - XYZ - Correspondence, 1946 (Box 3)
        Sections 22 and 23 from By-Laws, adopted at members' meetings of Oct. 27, 1930 as amendments (regarding purchasers and declaration of community sentiment regarding sale to "undesirables") (one sheet)
    - 1947
      - A - Correspondence, 1947 (Box 3)
      - B - Correspondence, 1947 (Box 3)
      - Burns Street Wall, 1947 (Box 8)
        Correspondence regarding repairs to retaining wall behind 92 and 98 Beach Knoll Road (blueprints)
      - C - Correspondence, 1947 (Box 8)
        Also copies of S.F. Hanes Co. - NY and Queens Electric L and P agreements for electric current dated June 12 and July 4
      - Circulars - Commercial fliers, 1945-1947 (Box 8)
      - Committee Reports, 1947 (Box 8)
        Law, architecture, annual meeting (agenda and meeting)
      - D - Correspondence, 1947 (Box 8)
      - E - Correspondence, 1947 (Box 8)
      - F - Correspondence, 1947 (Box 8)
      - G - Correspondence, 1947 (Box 8)
      - H - Correspondence, 1947 (Box 8)
      - I - Correspondence, 1947 (Box 8)
      - Insurance, 1947 (Box 8)
        Claims, contracts, policies, and correspondence
      - J - Correspondence, 1947 (Box 8)
      - K - Correspondence, 1947 (Box 8)
      - L - Correspondence, 1947 (Box 8)
      - Lampposts, 1942-1944 (Box 8)
        Locations and pole numbers - also copy of Three Year Report 1942, 1943, 1944, Jas. A. Burke, president Borough of Queens
      - M - Correspondence, 1947 (Box 8)
      - Mc - Correspondence, 1947 (Box 8)
      - N - Correspondence, 1947 (Box 8)
      - O - Correspondence, 1947 (Box 8)
      - Orders, 1947 (Box 8)
        Invoices, notices of annual meeting
      - P - Correspondence, 1947 (Box 8)
      - Parks - Park card records, 1947 (Box 8)
      - Q - Correspondence, 1947 (Box 8)
      - R - Correspondence, 1947 (Box 8)
      - S - Correspondence, 1947 (Box 8)
      - Streets, 1947 (Box 8)
        Correspondence regarding traffic control buses, signs, lighting (opinion of corporation counsel regarding expense dated July 19, 1947
      - T - Correspondence, 1947 (Box 8)
      - Treasurer's Reports - Bookkeeping and audit, 1947 (Box 8)
      - Trial Balance - Bookkeeping, 1947 (Box 8)
      - Upkeeping Committee, 1947 (Box 8)
        Reports, payrolls, inventories
      - V - Correspondence, 1947 (Box 8)
      - W - Correspondence, 1947 (Box 8)
      - Waivers - For various homeowners (architecture), 1946-1947 (Box 8)
      - XYZ - Correspondence, 1947 (Box 8)
    - 1948
      - A - Correspondence, 1948 (Box 3)
      - Annual Meeting, 1948 (Box 3)
        Minutes, program, reports, financial audit
      - Architectural Committee Reports, 1948 (Box 3)
      - B - Correspondence, 1948 (Box 3)
      - Family Judge Boyce, 1948 (Box 3)
        Correspondence from year 1937
      - C - Correspondence, 1948 (Box 3)
      - Circulars, 1948 (Box 3)
        Regarding handbills (esp. The Proprietor)
      - D - Correspondence, 1948 (Box 3)
      - E - Correspondence, 1948 (Box 3)
      - Eckman (Tract 2) (Box 3)
        NW corner Kessel and Ascan; dispute over maintenance charges, question of property being within the Gardens, correspondence beginning 1923-1950, correspondence concerns many problems of this sort along Whitson St., Kessel St. area (large folder)
      - F - Correspondence, 1948 (Box 3)
      - G - Correspondence, 1948 (Box 3)
      - H - Correspondence, 1948 (Box 3)
      - Help, 1946-1948 (Box 3)
        Regarding office employees, especially part-time
      - I - Correspondence, 1948 (Box 3)
      - Insurance, 1948 (Box 3)
        Policies, liability, correspondence, endorsements
      - J - Correspondence, 1948 (Box 29)
      - K - Correspondence, 1948 (Box 3)
      - L - Correspondence, 1948 (Box 3)
      - M - Correspondence, 1948 (Box 3)
      - Mc - Correspondence, 1948 (Box 3)
      - N - Correspondence, 1948 (Box 3)
      - Orders, 1948 (Box 3)
        Includes invoices
      - P - Correspondence, 1948 (Box 3)
      - Parks, 1948 (Box 2)
        Park card records and correspondence, memo to Gardens owners regarding snow removal, parking, etc.
      - R - Correspondence, 1948 (Box 2)
      - S - Correspondence, 1948 (Box 2)
      - Streets, 1948 (Box 2)
        Correspondence regarding outside tables and chairs (Forest Hills Inn), resurfacing, misc. correspondence, garages
      - T - Correspondence, 1948 (Box 2)
      - Treasurer's Report, 1948 (Box 3)
        Balance sheets, audit
      - U - Correspondence, 1948 (Box 3)
      - Upkeep Committee - -, 1948 (Box 3)
        Time sheets, reports, misc. correspondence
      - W - Correspondence, 1948 (Box 3)
      - Waivers, 1948 (Box 3)
        Pinto, Fischman, Howland, Humphreys, Bass, Turner
      - XYZ - Correspondence, 1948 (Box 3)
    - 1949
      - A - Correspondence, 1949 (Box 2)
      - Annual Meeting, 1949 (Box 2)
        Program, president's address, list of disgruntled people with complaints
      - B - Correspondence, 1949 (Box 2)
      - Boyce, 1946-1948 (Box 2)
        Law Committee Reports, correspondence
      - Bulova, 1949 (Box 2)
        Papers regarding proposed construction of Bulova Watch Factory at Queens Blvd. and Yellowstone Blvd.
      - C - Correspondence, 1949 (Box 2)
      - Car Licences, 1946-1949 (Box 2)
        regarding parking
      - Circulars, 1949 (Box 2)
        Correspondence regarding distribution of outside pamphlets
      - Committee Reports, 1949 (Box 2)
        Primarily architectural committee reports
      - D - Correspondence, 1949 (Box 2)
      - E - Correspondence, 1949 (Box 2)
      - F - Correspondence, 1949 (Box 2)
      - G - Correspondence, 1949 (Box 2)
      - H - Correspondence, 1949 (Box 2)
      - Mr. Hager (President), 1949 (Box 2)
      - I - Correspondence, 1949 (Box 2)
      - Insurance, 1949 (Box 3)
        Policies, injury reports, correspondence
      - J - Correspondence, 1949 (Box 2)
      - K -Correspondence, 1949 (Box 2)
      - L - Correspondence, 1949 (Box 2)
      - Lampposts, 1946-1949 (Box 2)
        Correspondence regarding new lampposts, moving of lampposts, letter to city regarding lampposts, lamppost repairs
      - Law Committee - Reports, correspondence, 1949 (Box 2)
      - M - Correspondence, 1949 (Box 2)
      - Mc - Correspondence, 1949 (Box 2)
      - N - Correspondence, 1949 (Box 2)
      - O - Correspondence, 1949 (Box 2)
      - Official Documents, 1913-1947 (Box 2)
        Knott Corp. Lease 1942; Notice regarding stakes in curb plots; correspondence regarding owners infringements in Gardens property; Telephone Company-Sage Foundations Homes Co. Agreement dated February 20, 1913 (original copy, regarding easements, rights of way); owners petition for bench in Flagpole park October 9, 1940; Report of Committee in Proposed Membership Corporation of Property Owners to take over control maintenance and restrictions at F.H.G. dated October 24, 1922; Certificate of Incorporation of Gardens Corporation December 7, 1922; Indenture January 1, 1923, between Sage Foundation Homes Co. and Russell Sage Foundation and Gardens Corp. (Gardens Corp. assumes rights and duties of Homes Company);Office memo regarding operating procedures; Agreement between Chapford Homes Corp. and Victor Palsits and Gardens Corporation (regarding property construction); contract for painting of flagpole, photocopy of letter from IRS regarding tax exempt status of FHGC dated as received November 11, 1942; Forest Hills Gardens Taxpayers Assoc. Constitution and By-Laws (no date); Certificate of Change of Name of Gardens Corp. to Forest Hills Gardens Corporation November 10, 1939; Constitution and By-Laws of Women's Club of Forest Hills (carbon copies); application for dump permit, dump permit for 1948; also permit for 1945, 1941, 1944, 1946; dump truck vehicles registration 1943, 1944, 1955, 1948; gasoline ration card for dump truck 1942
      - Orders, 1949 (Box 2)
        Orders and correspondence with vendors, information, publicity regarding changes in Forest Hills Inn, redecoration, etc.
      - P - Correspondence, 1949 (Box 2)
      - Parks, 1949 (Box 2)
        Park card records and correspondence
      - S - Correspondence, 1949 (Box 2)
      - Streets, 1949 (Box 2)
        Correspondence regarding paving, Armistice Day Parade, misc.
      - T - Correspondence, 1949 (Box 2)
      - Treasurer's Reports, June - December 1949 (Box 2)
      - U - Correspondence, 1949 (Box 2)
      - Upkeep Committee, 1949 (Box 2)
        Time sheets, committee reports, misc. correspondence
      - V - Correspondence, 1949 (Box 2)
      - W - Correspondence, 1949 (Box 2)
      - Wolosoff-Marjay Apartment (Box 2)
        Correspondence regarding proposed apartment in Burns St., just east of Station Square
      - XYZ - Correspondence, 1949 (Box 2)
    - 1950
      - A - Correspondence, 1950 (Box 19)
      - Architectural Submissions, 1945-1949 (Box 19)
      - Annual Meeting, 1950 (Box 19)
      - B - Correspondence, 1950 (Box 19)
      - Beggs Correspondence, 1950 (Box 29)
        regarding building of house in Olive Place and Groton Lane
      - C - Correspondence, 1950 (Box 19)
      - Committee Reports, 1950 (Box 19)
        Reports and minutes of Committees and FHGC
      - D - Correspondence, 1950 (Box 19)
      - Disability Insurance, 1950 (Box 19)
      - E & F - Correspondence, 1950 (Box 19)
      - G - Correspondence, 1950 (Box 19)
      - Gardens Committee, 1948 (Box 19)
        By-Laws of Gardens Assoc. of FHG, minutes of meetings
      - Grass, 1950 (Box 19)
        Lists of those who received grass seed
      - H - Correspondence, 1950 (Box 19)
      - Hager, 1950 (Box 19)
      - Heuston, 1950 (Box 19)
      - Infringements of Restrictions, 1945-1947 (Box 19)
      - Insurance, 1950 (Box 19)
      - J,K, & L - Correspondence, 1950 (Box 19)
      - Lampposts, 1950 (Box 19)
      - Law Committee, 1950 (Box 19)
        Includes reports
      - M, Mc, & N - Correspondence, 1950 (Box 19)
      - Newspaper Clippings, 1942-1950 (Box 19)
      - O & P - Correspondence, 1950 (Box 19)
      - Paint Approvals, 1936-1950 (Box 19)
      - Official Documents -, 1948-1949-1950 (Box 19)
        Vanderveer agreement dated May 17, 1923; permits for dump; service contracts; correspondence regarding owners' use of Gardens' property as their own
      - Orders, 1950 (Box 19)
      - Parks, 1950 (Box 19)
      - Mr. Priest, 1949-1950 (Box 19)
      - Publicity, 1947-1950 (Box 19)
      - Printing, 1948-1950 (Box 19)
      - Renewal of Restrictions, 1950 (Box 19)
        Copies of renewal agreement dated August 24, 1944, and notice of extension
      - R & S - Correspondence, 1950 (Box 19)
      - Social Security, 1942-1950 (Box 19)
      - Restriction Inquires, 1950 (Box 19)
      - Treasurer's Reports, 1950 (Box 19)
      - T - Correspondence, 1950 (Box 19)
      - Upkeep Committee, 1950 (Box 19)
      - V, W, & XYZ - Correspondence, 1950 (Box 19)
      - Renewal of Restrictions - Vanderveer, 1949 (Box 19)
      - Mr. Wagner (Chairman of Architectural Committee), 1938-1950 (Box 19)
    - Miscellaneous Correspondence
      - Miscellaneous Correspondence, 1930-1939 (Box 23)
        Primarily with vendors, employees of FHG, estimates from vendors
      - Miscellaneous Correspondence, 1932-1943 (Box 22)
        Especially Notices of violations of covenants and restrictions
      - Miscellaneous Correspondence, 1934-1942 (Box 22)
        Mostly from Mr. Spicer, and attorney and Director of the FHG Corp
      - Miscellaneous Correspondence, 1951-1954 (Box 17)
    - Vanderveer Tract
      Many of the files in Box 18 include some Atturbury correspondence.
      - A - Correspondence, 1923-1930 (Box 18)
      - B - Correspondence, 1924-1930 (Box 18)
      - C - Correspondence, 1923-1930 (Box 18)
      - E, F, and G - Correspondence, 1923-1930 (Box 18)
      - H - Correspondence, 1923-1930 (Box 18)
      - I, J, K, L - Correspondence, 1923-1930 (Box 18)
      - M, Mc, N, O, P - Correspondence, 1923-1930 (Box 18)
      - R - Correspondence, 1924-1930 (Box 18)
      - S - Correspondence, 1923-1930 (Box 18)
      - T - Correspondence, 1923-1930 (Box 18)
      - U, V, W, XYZ - Correspondence, 1923-1930 (Box 18)
      - E - Correspondence, 1932 (Box 22)
        Correspondence regarding Ehrlich residence, (Atterbury correspondence), (N.E. corner Harrow St. and Stafford Ave.)
      - H - Correspondence, 1931-1939 (Box 28)
      - I - Correspondence, 1938-1943 (Box 28)
      - J - Correspondence, 1932-1946 (Box 28)
      - K - Correspondence, 1931-1943 (Box 28)
      - L - Correspondence, 1933-1936 (Box 28)
      - M - Correspondence, 1931-1937 (Box 28)
      - M - Correspondence, 1935-1941 (Box 28)
      - O - Correspondence, 1931-1937 (Box 28)
      - P - Correspondence, 1931-1947 (Box 28)
      - R - Correspondence, 1931-1946 (Box 28)
      - S - Correspondence, 1931-1943 (Box 28)
        Regarding building in Vanderveer Tract and some general "S" correspondence 1931 and 1932
      - T - Correspondence, 1933-1935 (Box 28)
        Regarding building in Vanderveer land, especially near Herrick and Harrow Streets
    - Block 12
      - "Block 12", 1928-1929 (Box 17)
        Regarding proposed Leslie Apartment construction
      - Board of Estimate Petitions -, 1929 (Box 29)
        To change from a "D" to an "F" district to preserve "existing high class type of residential development" and prevent building of apartment on Block 12
      - Proposed Atterbury Development of Block 12, 1923-1929 (Box 29)
        Legal actions, correspondence, (picture)
      - Block 12 - Harris, 1925 (Box 29)
        Papers relating to the application regarding Block 12 (Atterbury scheme) - also shows earlier "Hanks Plan" of private homes for Block 12 (picture and article in FHG Bulletin Aug. 25, 1923 )
      - Block 12 Suit and Trial, 1929 (Box 29)
        To prevent Hariss' apartment development
      - Block 12 Suit, 1928 (Box 29)